Guide to the UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s UE.8.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- A Message to Sperry Workers from UE Regarding UE Inter-uion Rivalry, August 1965 (Box 6, Folder 400)
- Cartoon Calendar, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 400)
- GHR Workers Plan Bigger UE Vote on January 27 Regarding United Steel Workers of America Inter-union Rivalry, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 401)
- GE, Westinghouse Have Shortchanged Workers, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 401)
- Don't Get Caught in the IUE Mess Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, January 1966 (Box 6, Folder 402)
- Guidelines for Whom Regarding Wages, June 1966 (Box 6, Folder 402)
- What Should Union Officials Be Paid?, September 23, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 402)
- Here Is the Proof Regarding Red-baiting, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 403)
- Has Anyone Bothered Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and General Electric Organization, December 1966 (Box 6, Folder 403)
- Cartoon Calendar, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 403)
- Your Government Conducts an Election for You on the Job Regarding National Labor Relations Board, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 403)
- Break through on Pensions Regarding General Electric and Westinghouse, January 1967 (Box 6, Folder 404)
- 1966 GE Negotiations, February 1967 (Box 6, Folder 405)
- Your Right to Join UE Is Guaranteed by Law, August 1967 (Box 6, Folder 406)
- What...Again?, Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, October 1967 (Box 6, Folder 406)
- Organized Labor and the Black Worker, October 1967 (Box 6, Folder 407)
- You and Your Steward! (Box 6, Folder 407)
- Sample Constitution for UE Locals, April 1968 (Box 6, Folder 408)
- A Little Bit of UE History You Should Know Regarding Labor History, October 1968 (Box 6, Folder 409)
- Vietnam: The Inside Story, October 1968 (Box 6, Folder 409)
- All of Us Built America Regarding Blacks, October 1968 (Box 6, Folder 410)
- The Young Worker Challenges the Union Establishment, December 1968 (Box 6, Folder 410)
- UE Guide to Automation and the New Technology, March 1969 (Box 6, Folder 411)
- UE Guide on the Preparation and Conduct of a Strike, June 1969 (Box 6, Folder 412)
- The Secret Government Regarding Political Action, July 1969 (Box 6, Folder 412)
- Charter Member Certificate (Box 6, Folder 413)
- Congress and Religious Freedom (Box 6, Folder 413)
- B-B-H An Evil Bill: Analysis of the Ball-Burton-Hatch Bill Regarding Labor Legislation and Congress of Industrial Organization (Box 6, Folder 414)
- The China Lobby Vs. the Bill of Rights (Box 6, Folder 415)
- This Is Our Union Regarding Organization (Box 6, Folder 415)
- Working You to Pieces Regarding Piecework and United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America (Box 6, Folder 415)
- FE-CIO is the Harvester Workers Union Regarding Organization (Box 6, Folder 415)
- Where Your PAC Dollar Goes (Box 6, Folder 415)
- Some Answers Regarding Rent Control (Box 6, Folder 416)
- Well That Wraps Up This Place Regarding Unemployment and Erie General Electric (Box 6, Folder 417)
- Why Not? Regarding Erie General Electric and Negotiations (Box 6, Folder 417)
- The Case of the Trenton 6 (Box 6, Folder 417)
- Leland Stowe Regarding Radio Broadcasts (Box 6, Folder 417)
- Does Silence Mean Guilt Regarding Red-baiting (Box 6, Folder 417)
- List of Cooperating Manufacturers Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (Box 6, Folder 417)
- Big Vote for UE Regarding Star Expansion and International Brotherhood of ELectrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry (Box 6, Folder 418)
- The Game of Death Regarding Bookclub (Box 6, Folder 418)
- Your Secret Weapon Regarding Organization (Box 6, Folder 418)
- Wake Up CIO Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization Mine-Mill Inter-union Rivalry (Box 6, Folder 418)
- Sensational Crimes KeFauver Didn't Reveal Regarding Bookclub (Box 6, Folder 418)
- Season's Greetings (Box 6, Folder 418)
- UE Women Work for Freedom (Box 6, Folder 418)
- Okay, Blow Regarding Cartoons (Box 6, Folder 419)
- UE Guide for Servicemen's and Veteran's Welfare Committees (Box 6, Folder 420)
- UE Catalogue (Box 6, Folder 421)
- Flattery Will Get You Nowhere Regarding Local 407 and Women (Box 6, Folder 422)
- Be a Victory Planner Regarding World War II (Box 6, Folder 422)
- Your Local 89 Insurance Plan Regarding Staff Finances (Box 6, Folder 422)
- The Church Speaks Out for Labor (Box 6, Folder 423)
- Know Your Union Regarding Local 301 (Box 6, Folder 423)
- Are You With Us Regarding General Electric Organization (Box 6, Folder 423)
- The USA and the USSR Can and Must Get Along (Box 6, Folder 423)
- Manual on Workmen's Compensation Law (Box 6, Folder 424)
- What A Good Boy I Am, April 1948 (Box 6, Folder 425)
- Constitution of the Communist Party, October 1948 (Box 6, Folder 426)
- Peace...The Road To Full Employment, March 1952 (Box 6, Folder 427)
- They All Want Them - But Cheap!, April 1952 (Box 6, Folder 428)
- The Cold War: Fact, Myths, Consequences and Cure, February 1959 (Box 6, Folder 429)
- So Long, Partner!, February 1959 (Box 6, Folder 430)
- James Carey Dictator of the IUE, February 1959 (Box 6, Folder 431)
- GE Can Afford the Shorter Work Week, April 1959 (Box 6, Folder 432)
- This is IUE in Action...In Action for the Bosses!, May 1959 (Box 6, Folder 433)
- From Official US Government Documents, July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 434)
- Thou Hyocrite, July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 435)
- The 24th UE Convention General Officers Report, September 21-25, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 436)
- The 24th UE Convention Policy, September 21-25, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 437)
- The 24th Convention Proceedings, September 21-25, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 438)
- For the General Welfare, November 1959 (Box 6, Folder 439)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1959 (Box 6, Folder 440)
- The Times Demand a New Approach, December 1959 (Box 6, Folder 441)
- Time to Come Back, February 1960 (Box 6, Folder 442)
- UE and Government Work, March 7, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 443)
- Getting Out the News, September 1, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 444)
- Kowalski Bill Gives Workers Right to Move with Job, August 1, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 445)
- UE Members Did This Job!, January 1961 (Box 6, Folder 446)
- You Too Can Win with UE, March 27, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 447)
- Betrayal - Shameful Story of Steel's Five Month Strike, November 1961 (Box 6, Folder 448)
- Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 449)
- The Decline of the AFL-CIO, August 30, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 450)
- ABC's of UE, January 1963 (Box 6, Folder 451)
- What Happens to Your Dues Dollars, January 1963 (Box 6, Folder 452)
- UE The Union With a Difference You Can Feel!, March 1963 (Box 6, Folder 453)
- UE The Union With a Difference You Can Feel!, March 1959 (Box 6, Folder 453)
- Proud Record of An American Union, May 1964 (Box 6, Folder 454)
- Minimum Contract Requirements, September 1967 (Box 6, Folder 455)
- Los Dirigentes de UE, Ven, Piensan, y Sienten Igual que Usted!, February 1968 (Box 6, Folder 456)
- UE's Campaign That Saved a Plant, February 1968 (Box 6, Folder 457)
- Let's Unite, February 1968 (Box 6, Folder 458)
- 30 Years of UE Gains in GE, March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 459)
- Count Me In!, May 1968 (Box 7, Folder 460)
- The 33rd UE Convention Call, September 9-13, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 461)
- The 33rd UE Convention Credentials, September 1968 (Box 7, Folder 462)
- The 33rd UE Convention General Officers Report, September 9-13, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 463)
- The 33rd UE Convention Resolutions Adapted, September 9-13, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 464)
- Strike Benefits, September 9-13, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 465)
- Financial Corruption and Election Frauds in IUE, October 1968 (Box 7, Folder 466)
- Union Busting in Brockport: How GE Won, October 1968 (Box 7, Folder 467)
- UE Constitution, December 1, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 468)
- A Little Bit of UE History You Should Know, February 1969 (Box 7, Folder 469)
- Facts for GE-Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Cost of Living, April 1969 (Box 7, Folder 470)
- Facs for GE-Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Production and Wages, April 1969 (Box 7, Folder 471)
- Facts for GE-Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Health, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 472)
- UE Guide on Preparation and Conduct of a Strike, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 473)
- How to Improve Your Figure Without Going on a Diet, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 474)
- Strike Benefits, June 1969 (Box 7, Folder 475)
- UE Fact for GE 1969 Negotiations Regarding Retirement, June 1969 (Box 7, Folder 476)
- UE Facts for Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Retirement, June 1969 (Box 7, Folder 477)
- UE Facts for GE 1969 Negotiations Regarding Layoffs, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 478)
- UE Facts for Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Layoffs, June 1969 (Box 7, Folder 479)
- UE Facts for GE 1969 Negotiations Regarding Wages, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 480)
- UE Facts for Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Wages, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 481)
- UE Facts for General Electric Negotiations Regarding Medical Coverage, July, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 482)
- UE Facts for Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations Regarding Medical Coverage, July 1969 (Box 7, Folder 482)
- UE Facts for GE 1969 Negotiations, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 483)
- UE Facts for Westinghouse 1969 Negotiations, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 483)
- UE Facts for General Electric Negotiations, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 484)
- UE Facts for Westinghouse Negotiations, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 484)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, August 1969 (Box 7, Folder 485)
- UE Facts for General Electric Negotiations, September 1969 (Box 7, Folder 486)
- UE Facts for General Electric Negotiations, September 1969 (Box 7, Folder 486)
- General Electric...Knows No Shame!, October 1969 (Box 7, Folder 487)
- UE Policy on Strike Assistance, November 1969 (Box 7, Folder 488)
- Will the Real GE Please Stand Up!, November 1969 (Box 7, Folder 489)
- Why Are GE Workers on Strike?, November 1969 (Box 7, Folder 490)
- 34th UE Convention Officers Report, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 491)
- 34th UE Convention UE Policy, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 492)
- 34th UE Convention Proceedings, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 493)
- Nation's Leading Citizens Support GE Strikers, January 9, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 494)
- Blacks in the American Revolution, January 1970 (Box 7, Folder 495)
- UE News Martin Luther King Jr., January 1970 (Box 7, Folder 496)
- ...the First Negotiated Agreement with GE in 20 Years, March 1970 (Box 7, Folder 497)
- This Time We Kept Westinghouse Honest, April 1970 (Box 7, Folder 498)
- 102 Days, April 1970 (Box 7, Folder 499)
- 35 Years of Gains in UE, April 1970 (Box 7, Folder 500)
- What Should Union Officials Be Paid?, April 1970 (Box 7, Folder 501)
- Achievement Award, May 1970 (Box 7, Folder 502)
- 35 Years of UE Gains in Westinghouse, It Wasn't Easy Come!, May 1970 (Box 7, Folder 503)
- The 35th UE International Convention General Officers Reports, September 21-25, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 504)
- The 35th UE International Convention Policy, September 21-25, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 505)
- The 35th UE International Convention Call, September 21-25, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 506)
- The 35th UE International Convention Proceedings, September 21-25, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 507)
- Can the Worker Be Tricked into Betraying His Own Interest?, November 1970 (Box 7, Folder 508)
- Order Form Regarding Pamphlet, November 6, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 508)
- Labor Unity, December 1970 (Box 7, Folder 509)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 510)
- Benjamin Banneker, January 1971 (Box 7, Folder 511)
- Leadership Guide to UE Contract Negotiations, January 1971 (Box 7, Folder 512)
- ABC's of UE, March 1971 (Box 7, Folder 513)
- How Foreign is 'Foreign' Competition, May 1971 (Box 7, Folder 514)
- Social Security and You, June 1971 (Box 7, Folder 515)
- The 36th UE International Convention General Officers Report, August 30-September 3, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 516)
- The 36th UE International Convention Proceedings, August 30-September 3, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 517)
- The 36th UE International Convention Policy, August 30-September 3, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 518)
- Together We Win, November 1971 (Box 7, Folder 519)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1971 (Box 7, Folder 520)
- The Johnson Brothers: James Weldon and John Rosamond, January 1972 (Box 7, Folder 521)
- He Fought For His Union, January 1972 (Box 7, Folder 522)
- The Real Target of Nixon's Plan is Wages, February 1972 (Box 7, Folder 523)
- Phase II-It's Read Design, February 1972 (Box 7, Folder 524)
- A Record of UE Gains, February 1972 (Box 7, Folder 525)
- Esta es Historia! UE y sus Ganancias, February 1972 (Box 7, Folder 525)
- What Happens to Your Dues Dollars?, April 1972 (Box 7, Folder 526)
- UE Leaders See Things Your Way, May 1972 (Box 8, Folder 527)
- The 37th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 11-15, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 528)
- The 37th UE Convention Policy, September 11-15, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 529)
- Labor's Stake in the 1972 Elections, September 11-15, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 530)
- Catalogue of UE Publications and Other Aids, November 1972 (Box 8, Folder 531)
- Statement of Albert Fitzgerald on Pension Bills Before the House of Representatives, March 23, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 532)
- UE Guide to the Safe Handling of Solvents, May 1978 (Box 8, Folder 533)
- Inflation: Its Causes, Its Victims, November 1978 (Box 8, Folder 534)
- Procedure for Handling Local Union Books and Records, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Rules and Procedures for Local Trustees (Box 8, Folder 536)
- Procedure for Handling Local Union Books and Records (Box 8, Folder 536)
- UE Organizer's Manual, December 15, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 537)
- How Foreign is 'Foreign' Competition, May 1971 (Box 8, Folder 538)
- El Orgulloso Historical de Una Union Americana, August 1972 (Box 8, Folder 539)
- Catalogue of UE Publications and Other Aids, November 1972 (Box 8, Folder 540)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel!, November 1972 (Box 8, Folder 541)
- The 38th UE International Convention General Officers Report, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 542)
- The 38th UE International Convention Proceedings, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 543)
- The 38th UE International Convention Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 544)
- Alliance for Survival, February 1973 (Box 8, Folder 545)
- Alliance for Survival, March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 546)
- La UE es una Union o Sindicato con una Diferencia Palpable!, March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 547)
- Together We Win: Fight for Equality on the Job, March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 548)
- Unidos Venceremos: La Lucha por Igualdad en el Trabajo, March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 548)
- A Little Bit of UE History You Should Know..., May 1973 (Box 8, Folder 549)
- UE Delegation Visits the Soviet Union, May 1973 (Box 8, Folder 550)
- Unidos Venceremos: La Lucha por Igualdad en el Trabajo, July 1973 (Box 8, Folder 551)
- Los Dirigentes de UE, Ven, Piensan, y Sienten Igual que Usted!, July 1973 (Box 8, Folder 552)
- Your Right to Join UE is Guaranteed by Law!, August 1973 (Box 8, Folder 553)
- La Ley Asegura el Derecho de Ingresar a UE, August 1973 (Box 8, Folder 554)
- A Record of UE Gains, August 1973 (Box 8, Folder 555)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel!, August 1973 (Box 8, Folder 556)
- Safeguarding the Union's Integrity, November 1973 (Box 8, Folder 557)
- 38 Years of UE Gains in Westinghouse, November 1973 (Box 8, Folder 558)
- Together We Win, December 1973 (Box 8, Folder 559)
- The 39th UE International Convention General Officers Report, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 560)
- The 39th UE International Convention Proceedings, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 561)
- The 39th UE International Convention Policy, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 562)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 563)
- Leadership Guide to UE Contract Negotiations, January 1974 (Box 8, Folder 564)
- Thirst for Learning, January 1974 (Box 8, Folder 565)
- What Happens to Your Dues Dollar?, January 1974 (Box 8, Folder 566)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel, February 1974 (Box 8, Folder 567)
- Esta es Historia! UE y sus Ganancias, March 1974 (Box 8, Folder 568)
- Albert Fitzgerald Letter to Members, March 1974 (Box 8, Folder 569)
- Catalogue of UE Publications and Other Aids with James Matles June 4, 1974, Letter, June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 570)
- 38 Years of UE Gains in GE, September 1974 (Box 8, Folder 571)
- The Concept of Labor Unity in the 1970's, November 1974 (Box 8, Folder 572)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 573)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel!, January 1975 (Box 8, Folder 574)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, April 1975 (Box 8, Folder 575)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, June 1975 (Box 8, Folder 567)
- The 40th UE International Convention General Officers Report, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 568)
- The 40th UE International Convention Proceedings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 569)
- A Record of UE Gains, December 1975 (Box 8, Folder 570)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, December 1975 (Box 8, Folder 571)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 572)
- The 41st UE International Convention General Officers Report, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 573)
- The 41st UE International Convention Proceedings, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 574)
- The Role of Labor Today, January 1976 (Box 9, Folder 575)
- Thirst for Learning, June 1976 (Box 9, Folder 576)
- A Record of UE Gains, July 1976 (Box 9, Folder 577)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel!, July 1976 (Box 9, Folder 578)
- What Happens to Your Dues Dollar?, June 1976 (Box 9, Folder 579)
- Los Dirigentes de UE, Ven, Piensan, y Sienten Igual que Usted!, October 1976 (Box 9, Folder 580)
- UE Leaders See Things Your Way, October 1976 (Box 9, Folder 581)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, October 1976 (Box 9, Folder 582)
- The 42nd UE International Convention General Officers Report, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 583)
- The 42nd UE International Convention Policy, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 584)
- 40 Years of UE Gains in GE, February 1977 (Box 9, Folder 585)
- La UE es una Union o Sindicato con una Diferencia Palpable!, February 1977 (Box 9, Folder 586)
- A Record of UE Gains, April 1977 (Box 9, Folder 587)
- A Little Bit of UE History, May 1977 (Box 9, Folder 588)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, October 1977 (Box 9, Folder 589)
- Inflation: Unemployment Products of a War Economy, October 1977 (Box 9, Folder 590)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, October 1977 (Box 9, Folder 591)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel!, October 1977 (Box 9, Folder 592)
- ABC's of UE, November 1977 (Box 9, Folder 593)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1977 (Box 9, Folder 594)
- Facts and Figures on Unemployment and the Shorter Work Week, December 1977 (Box 9, Folder 595)
- The 43rd UE International Convention Officers Report, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 596)
- The 43rd UE International Convention Proceedings, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 597)
- The 43rd UE International Convention Policy, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 598)
- UE Guide to the Safe Handling of Solvents, May 1978 (Box 9, Folder 599)
- Too Many Hours!, August 1978 (Box 9, Folder 600)
- UE Guia para el Delegado de Taller, October 1978 (Box 9, Folder 601)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1978 (Box 9, Folder 602)
- Unidos Venceremos: La Lucha por Igualdad en el Trabajo, February 1979 (Box 9, Folder 603)
- District 6 and 7 UE Safety and Health Conference, March 24, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 604)
- ABC's of UE, March 1979 (Box 9, Folder 605)
- A Record of UE Gains, April 1979 (Box 9, Folder 606)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, April 1979 (Box 9, Folder 607)
- The Crisis in Health Care, April 1979 (Box 9, Folder 608)
- Your Friends and Neighbors at the Nearby Westinghouse Plant are on Strike..., July 1979 (Box 9, Folder 609)
- The 44th UE International Convention General Officers Report, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 610)
- The 44th UE International Convention Proceedings, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 611)
- The 44th UE International Convention Policy, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 612)
- The Crisis in Health Care, October 1979 (Box 9, Folder 613)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 614)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 615)
- The 45th International Convention General Officers Report, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 616)
- The 45th International Convention Proceedings, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 617)
- The 45th International Convention Policy, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 618)
- ABC's of UE Complete New Members' Kit, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 619)
- A Record of UE Gains, August 1980 (Box 9, Folder 620)
- UE The Union with a Difference You Can Feel, August 1980 (Box 9, Folder 621)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, August 1980 (Box 9, Folder 622)
- The 46th International Convention Officers Report, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 623)
- The 46th International Convention Proceedings, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 624)
- The 46th International Convention Policy, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 625)
- Together We Win The Fight for Full Equality for Women, April 1981 (Box 9, Folder 626)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 627)
- Tips on Putting Out Your Shop Paper, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 628)
- The 47th International Convention Officers Reports, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 629)
- The 47th International Convention Proceedings, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 630)
- The 47th International Convention Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 631)
- Los Objectivos y Estructura de UE, August 1982 (Box 9, Folder 632)
- How to Inspect Your Plant, October 1982 (Box 9, Folder 633)
- Half a Century of Gains in Westinghouse, January 1983 (Box 9, Folder 634)
- Los Objectivos y Estructura de UE, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 635)
- UE It's Aims and Structure, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 635)
- The 48th International Convention Officers Report Draft, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 636)
- The 48th International Convention Prodeedings, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 637)
- The 48th International Convention Policy, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 638)
- UE Leads the Fight Against Litton's Union Busting, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 639)
- The Fight to Save Jobs and Stop Plant Closings, February 1983 (Box 10, Folder 640)
- Half a Century of UE Gains in General Electric, March 1983 (Box 10, Folder 641)
- Basic Principles: Aggressive Struggle, Rank and File Control (Printed In-house), April 1983 (Box 10, Folder 642)
- UE Led the Way (Printed In-house), June 1983 (Box 10, Folder 643)
- Hazards in the Metal and Electrical Industries, October 1983 (Box 10, Folder 644)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1983 (Box 10, Folder 645)
- The 49th International Convention Officers Report, September 1984 (Box 10, Folder 646)
- The 49th International Convention Proceedings, September 1984 (Box 10, Folder 647)
- The 49th International Convention Policy, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 648)
- Foreign Competition - Made in the US, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 649)
- Automation and Jobs - Who Decides?, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 650)
- Sexual Harassment: Fighting a Job Hazard, April 1984 (Box 10, Folder 651)
- UE Convention and By-laws, December 1984 (Box 10, Folder 652)
- The 50th International Convention Officer's Report, September 1985 (Box 10, Folder 653)
- The 50th International Convention Proceedings, September 1985 (Box 10, Folder 654)
- The 50th International Convention Proceedings, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 655)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 656)
- UE The Union With a Difference You Can Feel, May 1985 (Box 10, Folder 657)
- Highlights Tentative Agreement Between UE and Westinghouse, July 22, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 658)
- It's Happened This Way..., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 659)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 659)
- The 51st International Convention Proceedings, September 1986 (Box 10, Folder 659)
- The 51st International Convention Policy, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 659)
- Staw Wars: The Missing Link to a First Strike?, May 1986 (Box 10, Folder 660)
- Make Labor Rights Violations an Unfair Trade Practice!, September 1986 (Box 10, Folder 661)
- The 52nd International Convention Officer's Reprot, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 662)
- The 52nd International Convention Proceedings, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 662)